const STORE=[
    {
        question: "Who was not a Stark?",
        selections: [
            "Arya",
            "Jon",
            "Sansa",
            "Theon"],
        answer: "Theon"},
    {
        question: "What was the name of Jon's direwolf?",
        selections: [
            "Summer",
            "Shaggydog",
            "Nymeria",
            "Ghost"],
        answer: "Ghost"},
    {
        question: "How did Daenerys' eggs hatch? When they were placed in: ",
        selections: [
            "A funeral pyre",
            "An oven",
            "A hearth",
            "A campfire"],
        answer: "A funeral pyre"},
    {
        question: "Who did Sansa not marry?",
        selections: [
            "Tyrion",
            "Littlefinger",
            "Ramsey Bolton"],
        answer: "Littlefinger"},
    {
        question: "Which is not one of Daenerys' dragons names?",
        selections: [
            "Drogon",
            "Rhaegal",
            "Viserion",
            "Vhagar"],
        answer: "Vhagar"},
    {
        question: "How many actors portrayed The Mountain?",
        selections: [
            "One",
            "Two",
            "Three",
            "Four"],
        answer: "Three"},
    {
        question: "What explosive substance was utilized in the Battle of Blackwater Bay?",
        selections: [
            "Greek fire",
            "Wildfire",
            "Dynamite",
            "Green fire"],
        answer: "Wildfire"},
    {
        question: "Besides dragonglass what other material can defeat a White Walker?",
        selections:[
            "Wildfire",
            "Jon Snows piercing gaze",
            "Valyrian Steel",
            "Water"],
        answer: "Valyrian Steel"},
    {    
        question: "Which god does Arya briefly serve in Esos?",
        selections:[
            "The God of Death/The Many-Faced God",
            "The Mother",
            "The Warrior",
            "The Old Gods"],
        answer: "The God of Death/The Many-Faced God"},
    {
        question: "Who did not help conspire to kill Joffrey Baratheon?",
        selections:[
            "Sansa",
            "Lady Onella",
            "Littlefinger"],
        answer: "Sansa"}
    
];